Women's City Club
DC Public Library, Special Collections
Women's City Club Records
1919-1974
DC Public Library, Special Collections
11 linear feet; 20 boxes
032
Detailed Description of the Collection
- Series 1: Meeting Minutes, 1919-1982
  - Untitled, 1919-1921 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1921-1923 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1923-1926 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1925-1929 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1929-1932 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1931-1934 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1934-1938 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1938-1944 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1944-1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1944-1954 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1954-1960 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Untitled, 1963-1972 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Series 2: Administrative Materials, 1940-1974
  - History, Undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Columbia Lighthouse for the Blind report, 1972 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - General files, 1972-1980 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Clippings, Undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Financial records, Undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Financial records, 1936-1948 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Club bulletins and yearbooks, 1948-1952 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - By-laws and articles of incorporation, 1949-1952 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Nominations, 1949-1952 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - House rules, 1952-1954 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and reports, 1950s (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Series 3: Photographs, 1919-1974
  - Miss Ellen Spencer Mussey, 1919 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Mabel Lyman Swormstedt, 1923-1924 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Dr. A. Frances Toye, 1924-1926 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Dearn Grace Hayes Riley, 1926-1928 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Euterpe Fitzgerald Chance, 1928-1930 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Mrs. Glaydes Middlemiss, 1940-1962 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Mrs. Lee Corbin, 1930-1932 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Pearle Mesta, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Series 4: Scrapbooks and Memorabilia, 1925-1968
  - Community Improvement Award Certificate, 1972-1974 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Sign, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbooks, 1925-1926 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1936-1938 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Scrapbooks, 1938 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Scrapbooks, 1941 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Scrapbooks, 1942-1946 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Scrapbooks, 1947 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Scrapbooks, 1948 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Scrapbooks, 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Register of Sunday Tea Guests, 1940 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Collection of original poems, 1943 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Series 5: Oversize
  - Oversized scrapbook, 1930-1936 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Receipt books, 1962-1974 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Framed photograph of Dorothy B. Marvin, Undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Framed photograph of unidentified woman, Undated (Box 20, Folder 3)